* VPN Services

    iTop VPN for Windows 11
    
    * Best-in-class encryption & no-log policy
    * Private access to the global Internet
    * Lightning speed to surf the internet
    * Protect data with split tunneling
    
    Download Now Get 86% OFF

    iTop VPN Mac
    
    * Military-level Encryption Guarantee
    * Quick Access to Websites, Apps, Games, etc.
    * Free VPN for MacBook and All Macs
    
    Download Now Get 86% OFF

    iTop VPN for iOS
    
    * Best-in-class encryption
    * Unlimited data
    * Lightning speed
    
    [Download Now](https://goto.itopvpn.com/downloadcenter?product=itopios) Get 86% OFF

    iTop VPN for Android
    
    * Best-in-class encryption
    * Unlimited data
    * Lightning speed
    
    [Download Now](https://goto.itopvpn.com/downloadcenter?product=itopandroid) Get 86% OFF

* Utility
    * [
        
        **iTop Data Recovery**
        
        Fast data recovery software.](https://www.itopvpn.com/data-recovery-software)
    * [
        
        **iTop PDF**
        
        Full-featured simple PDF editor.](https://pdf.itopvpn.com/)
    * [
        
        **iTop Easy Desktop FREE**
        
        Free desktop organizer and wallpaper.](https://www.itopvpn.com/itop-easy-desktop)
    * [
        
        **iTop Private Browser**
        
        Safe and private browser with VPN.](https://www.itopvpn.com/vpn-browser)
    * [
        
        **Smart Game Booster FREE**
        
        FPS booster and game optimizer.](https://gamebooster.itopvpn.com/index.php)
    * [
        
        **IOTransfer**
        
        Professional iPhone transfer software.](https://iotransfer.itopvpn.com/)
    * [
        
        **iTop Screenshot FREE**
        
        Best screenshot software without limits.](https://recorder.itopvpn.com/screenshot)
    * [
        
        **DualSafe Password Manager**
        
        Secure and advanced password manager.](https://www.itopvpn.com/dualsafe-password-manager)
* Blog

Privacy Policy

Last Updated: June 14, 2022

This Privacy Policy applies to the websites (“itopvpn.com”), its sub-websites, the software or applications, and any accompanying services, (“ the Services”, “our Services”, "iTop", "We", "us" , or “Our”), owned and operated by iTop Inc.

The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you of what information we collect, use and share when you visit our Site and/or use our Services. Your privacy is extremely important to us and we are committed to protecting your privacy all the time.

By visiting our websites, by submitting your data to us, and by accessing, installing and/or using the Services, you confirm that you have read this Privacy Policy and agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy. If you disagree with the rules of this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Services.

What Information We Collect

All the information listed below that we collect is used for providing and improving the Services. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. To maximize your privacy, iTop only collects the minimum information to provide a better user experience.

Service Data

In order to provide you with our products and Services, we collect limited personal information from customers who register with our services including a username or email address and phone number for the purpose of account verification and providing Services.

For the account you registered for our Services, iTop does not have access to or knowledge of the account password and the data you saved in the account (such as the data you saved in DualSafe Password Manager, iTop Screen Recorder, iTop Screenshot, and other iTop services). We do not have access to and/or the ability to decrypt your saved data under any circumstance. Our Zero-Knowledge encryption model ensures that only you can decrypt your stored information. We have no way of accessing or decrypting your data. [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

Customer Service and Technical Service

We may collect or ask you to provide necessary information when you reach us by email or by requesting online support.

This information may include, without limitation, your name, your email address, your order reference, how you use our service, your computer or device information such as hardware and system version, crash logs, etc. In general, we collect no more information than is required in order to investigate the issue you encounter. We will only use such information to provide customer service and/or troubleshoot the technical problem you are experiencing.

Cookies

When you visit our websites, we may store cookies on your computer (as well as other tracking technologies like web beacons and pixels) in order to facilitate and customize your use of our websites. A cookie is a small data text file, which a website stores on your computer's hard drive (if your web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to us. Our cookies may store information regarding your account information. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, but such disabling may cause some of the features of our websites would not operate properly and your online experience may be limited.

We do not log your activity while you are utilizing the Services, including your original IP address, browsing history, traffic destination, DNS queries, or transferred data.

Third-Party Tools

To analyze website and application events from our users in order to understand how our Services function, we use some third-party tools. Here are the third-party tools we use, how we use them, and their privacy policies:

· Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a web analytics service provided by Google. iTop uses Google Analytics cookies to help us understand the use of our Site by our visitors, compile reports on your website activity, and provide other services relating to website activity and internet usage. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google. Google's privacy policy is available at https://policies.google.com/privacy

· Microsoft App Center on Windows OS

Microsoft App Center belongs to Microsoft. This was used to do beta distribution, crash reporting, user metrics, feedback, and more. Its privacy policy is available at https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/PrivacyStatement

· Google Firebase Analytics on iOS

Firebase helps us understand how people interact with our Services by providing insight on app usage and user engagement. You can find its privacy policy at https://policies.google.com/privacy

· Google Fabric Crashlytics on iOS

This Google tool can collect, analyze, and organize app crash reports, thus to help us improve application stability and improve your experience. Its implementation doesn’t contain any information that can personally identify you. You can find its privacy policy at https://policies.google.com/privacy

· haveibeenpwned.com

DualSafe Password Manager uses this API to inform privacy leaks if there is any. You can find its privacy policy at: [https://haveibeenpwned.com/Privacy](https://haveibeenpwned.com/Privacy)

Placing Orders

When you purchase our products or services, the billing is handled by a third-party service provider, who is acting on our behalf; thus, you will make your purchase from the service provider directly, and not from iTop. The handling of your personal information will be governed by any privacy policy or terms of service published by the service provider.

The service provider may request billing information such as your name, email address, home or work address, telephone or mobile phone number, payment information including credit card number, expiration date, security code, name of your issuing bank, etc. The purpose of this information is to fulfill orders, process payment, deliver products, provide customer service, and the like. The third-party service provider may transmit some of your personal information to us, but not including payment information. We may use the information we receive to verify your subscription, to contact you about the status of your order, for renewal of your subscription, if applicable.

We have agreements with all the third-party service providers that they will not use personal information of our users for their own marketing purposes, and will not share this information with other parties.

Use of Social Networks

If you choose to ‘share’ iTop products with friends through Facebook, Twitter or other social networks, you might be sent cookies from these websites. We don’t control the setting of these cookies, so please check those websites for more information about their cookies and how to manage them

How We Use Your Information

We use your information in order to provide you with the Services. Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To provide the requested service

Some data are necessary to deliver the service you requested.

To improve our websites and service

We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

To improve customer service

Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

To process transactions

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

To send periodic emails

The email address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can follow the detailed unsubscribe instructions that we included at the bottom of each email.

How We Share Your Information

iTop does not share or disclose your personal information to any third parties with two exceptions as below:

Third-Party Service Providers

We may hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, hosting websites, processing transactions, or performing statistical analysis of our services. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.

Legal Requirements

In the event we are served with valid subpoenas, warrants, or other legal documents (for example, documents concerning the sale of all or part of our business), or where applicable law compels us to comply, or when we are required to defend the rights or property of the iTop Inc., including the security of our products and services, and the personal safety, property, or other rights of our customers and employees, or a request for data with the purpose of identifying and/or preventing credit card fraud, we may share your personal data as collected above.

Security and Confidentiality

We understand and accept our responsibility to protect your data. Our employees are subject to confidentiality obligations. We use industry-standard information, security tools, and measures, as well as internal procedures and strict guidelines to prevent information misuse and data leakage, but we cannot guarantee that our systems will be absolutely safe (actually no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure). If you become aware of any potential data breach or security vulnerability, you are requested to contact us immediately. We will use all measures to investigate the incident, including preventive measures, as required.

In addition, it is extremely important that you understand that it is your responsibility to protect the security of your password for the account registered for iTop Services. The password should be strong and unique and not easy to be guessed. It should be known by you only. It is equally important that you keep a copy in a safe place for your own reference, because you will need your password to decrypt all the data you saved in our Services. We are unable to decrypt your data.

How to Access, Control and Delete Your Data

You can add, remove, edit, and change any data that are saved in iTop Services, at any time, by logging into your account.

You also have the right to deactivate and delete your iTop account at any time by contacting us [here](https://www.itopvpn.com/support). However, some information may remain in archived/backup copies to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

For the information processed by the third party partners, you have the right to access your personal information. If you want to access, correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data on our third party partner's platform, you should contact them directly as they are the data controllers and iTop has no control of those information.

Information Warranty Disclaimer

Notwithstanding anything else in this Policy, we are not responsible for the accuracy, correctness, and security of any of the information we gather, store, and disclose to you or to anyone else.

Our policy only addresses the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. To the extent you disclose your information to other parties or sites throughout the internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Accordingly, we encourage you to read the terms and conditions and privacy policy of each third party that you choose to disclose information to.

Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products, and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

Changes to This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page. The last revision will be reflected in the "Last Updated" heading. Any changes to this policy will be posted on the Site. Your continued use of the Services following any such changes will be considered as your consent to the amended Privacy Policy.

How to Contact Us

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or believe that iTop has not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](https://www.itopvpn.com/support) and we will make efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.

Subscribe to Our Newsletter

  Subscribe

_√_

Subscribe to our newsletter to stay updated every moment.

Success! Check your inbox or spam folder for a confirmation email from us :）

Oops! Please enter a valid email address.

 English

* Product
    
* Company
    
* Help

    Partner

© 2024 Orange View Limited. All rights reserved.

Subscribe to Our Newsletter

  Subscribe

_√_

Subscribe to our newsletter to stay updated every moment.

Success! Check your inbox or spam folder for a confirmation email from us :）

Oops! Please enter a valid email address.

* Product

* Company

* Partner

* Help

 English

© 2024 iTop. All rights reserved.

iTop uses cookies to improve content. Find out more on our [Privacy Policy](https://www.itopvpn.com/privacy)

OK, I got it

_x_

[

VPN](https://www.itopvpn.com/vpn-android)[

Record](https://recorder.itopvpn.com/)[

Recover](https://www.itopvpn.com/data-recovery-software)[

Protect](https://www.itopvpn.com/top-data-protector)
